<ModMetaData>

	<name>DocWorld</name>
	<author>Dr_Zhivago</author>
	<url>https://github.com/DrZhivago1/DocWorld</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.1</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>drzhivago.docworld</packageId>
  <description>
One of the most ambitious efforts to reorganize RimWorld/Mods into a cleaner, better functioning, and intuitive system. This mod patches, fixes, and adds content to many mods (including but not limited to plain old vanilla RimWorld).

&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;
    * New Architect tabs and organizes Architect menu
    * New drop down menus
    * Balances recipes for various items
    * Underground power conduits
    * Enhances miniaturisation abilities
    * Increased "stuffable" items
    * Lights are now more efficient with power usage
    * Greatly improves inter-mod compatibility

[Link to GitHub]
  https://github.com/DrZhivago1/DocWorld/releases

[Link to Ludeon]
  https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=47165.msg447416#msg447416

[The Doctor's World mod collection]
  https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1568763074
    
&lt;size=24&gt;Credits&lt;/size&gt;
    &lt;b&gt;Alex Il Tabaccaio&lt;/b&gt; for the encouragement and helpful additions.
    &lt;b&gt;Ashnal&lt;/b&gt; for the encouragement and helpful additions.  
    &lt;b&gt;Chicken Plucker&lt;/b&gt; for the awesome picture of the Doctor.
    &lt;b&gt;jptrrs&lt;/b&gt; for the encouragement and helpful additions.  
    &lt;b&gt;Lanilor&lt;/b&gt; for helping me learn xpath patching on the Discord.  
    &lt;b&gt;Mehni&lt;/b&gt; for his time and patience on the Discord.  
    &lt;b&gt;NotFood&lt;/b&gt; for showing the way of the dragon.  
    &lt;b&gt;RedistHeat&lt;/b&gt; the mod, not a person, for cooler textures.  
    &lt;b&gt;ruyanve&lt;/b&gt; for the encouragement and helpful additions.   
    &lt;b&gt;Sunlace&lt;/b&gt; for hidden conduit idea.  
    &lt;b&gt;Taranchuk&lt;/b&gt; for the encouragement and helpful additions.  
    &lt;b&gt;XeoNovaDan&lt;/b&gt; for the encouragement and helpful additions.  
    &lt;b&gt;Yehn&lt;/b&gt; for helping with xml on the Discord.  
    &lt;b&gt;Architect Textures&lt;/b&gt; &lt;i&gt;Smartline&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;eucalyp&lt;/i&gt;, and free pics @ https://www.flaticon.com/  
    &lt;b&gt;All the beautiful mod creators without whom these patches wouldn't do much.&lt;/b&gt;
  </description>

</ModMetaData>
